HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM HMM H
Excuse me, sir, how?
Squirt, squirt. Oh, no. Here's what I'll address.
So, like, you know, this woman, Christine,
has been harassing me.
Like, not even just harassing me,
because I've loved her alone.
Other people have said things, you know.
I've loved her alone. But you know what she's saying.
So, they put up in this chat,
and I like food stamps or whatever,
not actual, like, you know,
like the streamer named Food Stamps.
I like him. And I don't know who was in charge of Harry's.
Harry is the innocuous or something was in charge.
But they put her comment, why does everyone hate me?
Because they're stupid, and maybe the people that do,
they just don't know, they're just ignorant,
they're followers, they believe everything they hear,
they don't follow up, they don't, I don't know,
they're just dumb, in my opinion, in my opinion.
But anyway, so yeah, but they put her comment
on the screen, something like, oh, I support beating women.
and, you know, all this stuff.
So I just went, then they put that on the screen.
They put it up on the screen, like, oh, here's the,
here's the right, like, and so I slanted her back.
You don't look back.
But just as an ridiculous way,
I said something unsure too, but what happened?
They immediately delete that comment,
hers was on the screen.
I don't know, maybe they, but I'm just saying,
is that if you're gonna let people slander me
and like then publicize it, I'll slander her right back.
That's fair, fair.
Hey, Christine Christine's on in here. She doesn't watch anymore. What do you do? You're saluting to her?
What does she what does she like give you five bucks or something like that?
But she'll do she'll like start donating and then and then um, you know
Shout out to second he's off. Hey, KZ. Go wash your ass to McDonald's. Okay. She's not here. Go wash your ass to McDonald's and
Yep, take a break. Hold on. What was that? I'm confused
Yeah, your scene is getting you cabinets in her. Well, I mean, I don't know
I mean, I'm only even like you'll go into like, you know, I don't know anything about her house
I mean, it's like I mean other than you know, I was so nice to
Her dog is that she just has to keep slandering me and saying horrible horrible thing like the worst thing
You know, she's just taking a you know, I'll have to send her a cease and desist next
Then she she can send me a cease and desist too. I mean, that's the thing about cease and desist
you're like stop stop saying this pretty good thing, but
her house is sinking into the ground. Oh, that's unfortunate. That's unfortunate. Well, maybe
if she's a little bit nicer, you know, she'll get some good karma, but she's gonna go out and
attack me for no reason. I'm gonna find that. Let me see if I can find that episode. Like, uh,
Tripp kicked a long time ago. You see this exists. Tripp, Tripp kicked it a long time ago. Let me
see. Hold on. I had an episode with Chris summary. I need to find it. And it's probably figured out
Crystal Marie was on one night and started saying so the first time I met Christine Christine told me she's like oh my name
Not even really Christine. I just named myself after that Stephen King movie about the car. Yeah
Okay
What do you mean that the car that murders?
Okay, hold on the episode. Let me see if I can find in my archives. Okay
Let me see see a couple transcripts. Let me see crystal Marie
A trip gave me a whole thing about it. Let me see if I can find this. Just worry. Hi Rudy! Let me see.
Um okay I think I found it. Let's see what I have here. I need to find it on my studio.
Hi Rude! So how's everyone doing today otherwise? Hi Rudy! Hi! Hi! Hi Rudy! Let's see if I can find this.
Hi hi hi! Okay here it is. Classic.
It is so sweet, huh?
Hi, Roode.
We're so sweet.
Okay, here, this is the classic episode.
It was awesome.
Now, a little bit with Bita, I think, and...
Oh, no.
So it was one way, and then it goes the other, but...
Right, I mean, even the same day,
like this, I think one of the,
like the day we got in our most recent fight,
like I talked to her like, I think earlier in the day,
and we had like a great conversation.
We just had like, we like,
get along fine on the phone,
and then it's like, when she does the show,
Her show is like a lot of people are attacking me in there. I've learned to start to this like
Block them though. I'm not a modern her shadow anymore. So I don't have to
Have to like, you know, you know, but she's mad at me. She's really mad at me now
I have but I also have a video to play with a crystal Murray is so funny, you know crystal Murray
Here it is. You will not believe what happens. Okay. Well, you might believe it, but you know, you know,
If you're not
Expecty and he will not move. Okay, so let me see.
Restricted for a second. Okay, okay, ready?
Is it up? Yep. Take on the banner real quick.
You see it's going to be the X-Files. Watch this. There we go.
I'm going to shut up Casey.
I'll take myself off, but enjoy. I'll just scan a game that blocks you.
Well, he was in the white, that white fantasy game that did hurt me.
That was trying to kill me. I guess she was like a lot of criminal record.
And she's trying to cover it up, so, um, or just gonna break it.
Yeah, but you're not like Christine. I mean, no, I'm not like Christine. We all know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. She's got a big criminal record. She's about to get fucked.
What does she do?
She kills kids.
Oh, my God. Chris, don't. No, no, no, no, no.
And you know like that first thing I told you these people like that the fucking I told you like that the same people or
Like you wouldn't even believe that their age. You know what I mean? It's like
Well, I'm saying that that I wouldn't understand that a bitch
It that would act like that like that is like I guess she she's like a lot of criminal record
And she's trying to cover it up. So
We're just gonna break it
Yeah, yeah, yeah, she's got a big criminal record she's got to get fucked
Cat friends. No, no, no. Yep
Why what'd she do? She was a criminal? Yeah, she's a bad criminal
What'd she do? She killed kids. Oh my god, please don't no no no no no no no
You're gonna go she kills goats
Well, he puts them in, they put them in these sex trafficking rings, and her friend probably fucking her own product, and we're gonna get them all fucking caught real quick.
Yeah, they're not trying to help people, they're trying to get people fucking caught up.
That's sick.
Christine does this?
Yeah
Why do you think that she says that she's a part that she works for
fucking listen, she says that she is
What's it called, you know first aid what do you know nurse and she also says that that she's
First line security
Yeah, she says she's a security guard the mall the weekend, right?
No, she said that or is that what she told you?
She said she works with Alex at the mall
I'm here
But yeah, so she's she's false in security so she can
do other bad things with other parts of law.
So yeah, she's fucked.
I'm having a hard time.
Hopefully, like, you know, she'll get a third.
No, she's going to jail forever.
Shit.
I wouldn't really mind going to jail forever, if it was me,
because I'd finally get like a city's five sex,
three showers and stuff.
Yeah, but you're not a bad guy,
and you would like Excel because you're like a man.
But no, you're...
I mean, you know, we're those people that that use the system, you know, that say that they're doing like companies and like
And they say that they're getting this people houses and they don't
And they got like they're giving the difference in so many money and because
Uh, yeah, you know, this is all fucking false and that fucking bitch is about to go down and she's about to have no job
Yeah, they're all doing bad, you know, it's it's about it's an all system
It's a bad system that's about to go down from georgia to
airton, florida
What are they gonna do?
Well they're about to get him to go to prison.
Is that going to happen soon? Or this year? What do you think?
I don't know how that works.
Who's going to go first? Epstein or uh?
Christine. 100%.
Which Christine was here? We got to this guy every time we're talking
about Christine and uh
Well, because she did bad stuff online, and it's caught up to her.
But she's doing it, but I can't imagine Christine doing anything bad online where she's on a
doorstep.
Well, because you can't pay people, you can't pay people to abuse you, people.
That's the good part.
Yeah, that's a long this is consensual right and that's I say I want you yeah, so and when it's on video and it's yeah
It's against a lot when it's been by five people
Yeah, and on different networks, we are not even the same fucking people
It doesn't matter because we're not all the same
Well, we couldn't out because it's it's her work. It's what she did
It's out of her it's out of her her her own
Device Christina, I really hope that out of her own device. You know what you mean device, you know
People do bad things under their own device
Yes
So you hacked Christine well, that's a little too
Never I would never know she fucking had to try to do bad things to me
Christine I need you years ago years ago. I got this years ago
Doesn't even know I got all her shit years ago. How many years I told you this I told you this I tried to tell you this
This is why I did not want the fucking flaggery.
I said, when I seen the thing with the,
then I knew the gods and you don't even know what I knew.
Which is our god?
Well, no, they have like, they, you know,
they're friends with people that aren't friends with us.
And you know.
Like criminals?
Yeah
Did you hear Chris K is gonna want to come over and masturbate with me not just be
I don't know. I don't like that
I shouldn't do that
He has $1000 in cash. He wants to come over. Well, I would say don't do that because he was one of the ones that was
Well, it's the Bernesee gang that had like a lot of money to murder me.
But yeah, he came over there at night and he was like, hey, he's like, money talks.
He's like, how does everyone want to see the second I do a chatter?
Well, then he said he says a lot of things and he acts a lot weird.
Yeah.
I know just be very
Told that he might just try to beat me up, but then I watch a video and I'll be very where do you be very where I?
Watch him fighting with a black dwarf in the black door, but so I'm not even scared
He bought a dwarf in Las Vegas and he lost
Well, I seen something else where he tried to act like he was a cop. Yeah
I'm sorry, I mean interrupt. Yeah
When he did that that meant
He's worthy of death. Oh
Like oh, well, it's like I think he's just ignorant. Maybe you know, it's like yeah, but that's pretty ignorant
Pretty ignorant, but I mean we're all we're all gonna you know pass away something
No, we're all we're all I'm saying he he deserves it
Hopefully maybe he can change his ways that'd be good. You live in two people changing their ways. I don't
You don't okay, so it's Chris can a gang that stalks you
Well, he was in the white that white spurnicy gang that did hurt me that was trying to kill me
You know that aren't you without you're like a part of spanish or something. They don't like spanish. That's kind of weird
No, I wasn't in it. He was in a gang that is against me
Why were they against you though? Oh?
They were trying to kill me
They did with George or stinks is backing you up, and they're all saying yes, they did
Why would they want to do that? I don't do they want to kill me. Do you think or unalive me?
Well at that time
People were saying that I was married to a black guy, which I was never married engage anything to a black guy
I would love to be married to it's black. Oh my gosh. Look how bad I look
You're beautiful. I should put makeup on
Just put on a filter put on a filter on the camera. I will put on makeup for you
No, I'm not doing that.
And it's like, is a...
I don't like to sit there and like, I like to be like albondy with my hands off.
And then your pants.
And then I like to unbutton them, like just like, just like this, you know what I mean?
Put your hands down in your, your um, nether regions.
Oh my god.
Okay, careful Chris, okay, so I don't want to get in trouble.
No.
No, but what I'm saying is that these people are being very mean. Oh my gosh
I look terrible. See, this is why I don't want to be on there
Now you're beautiful you are beautiful
Really great stomach
Yeah, I do too look at mine. You see mine. Oh, no, I want to show mine
That's good.
Great.
Thank you.
Okay.
Someone said take off the...
Yeah.
You can show yours.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
I got like...
Oh, guys.
I don't like non-baggy bands.
Okay.
Do you have a hole in your jeans?
It looks like there's a little hole in your jeans.
Okay.
That looks like mine.
Really twins.
Hold on.
I'll put myself back on.
Guys, let's compare.
Okay.
That looks like mine.
Really twins.
Hold on.
Put myself back on.
Guys, let's compare.
Is it good?
No, I'm fat.
I'm fat. I've got bloated, dude.
I just ate six cookies.
I feel fat, too.
I think I'm...
I just had McDonald's Big Mac and...
And I will say, too.
You won't have to worry about me you might have to worry
about your family from
their
family trees
That's what I said
You might have to worry
When you say shit about me you might have to worry about
three
you get the job so you get the job so you get the job how was that and that was pretty
You have a brand new deck of carp in this deck to a reading for the person that sponsors
that and two other people that they can choose for $10.
If you can just hang out and listen to more music, I'll make a video.
Yeah.
It's a good idea.
I would like to be doing some more readings and actually I'm actually pretty on demand
on Instagram and on TikTok.
Might need to slowly keep changing the format until just the right people are here, right?
You might notice I did I did re-brand the channel
Who this channel? I think it was like you wake in tarot
This particular channel the name is now like you're weakens TV for this channel
Tiktok is still like you wake in tarot. I do most of the tarot on there anyway, but
Yeah, I'm building my empire. I have a book
I'm doing a tarot deck. I'm doing some other consulting and things like that. So, oh yeah,
I did watch Alex. I don't like to interrupt because I don't want to do the extraction,
but yeah, she was doing good and like, you know, they played some stuff on Sandman,
it was like Alex, me and the beat was there and you know, it's sad and I am sad and I don't,
I think Pita thinks I hate her, but I would say Pita hated me. That's like the fusing part,
I hope that it was all a big misunderstanding, but just, or just like, I don't know, maybe
she's not allowed to use the word empath, okay?
So you know what?
You're not allowed to be in the chat, Joe, because you know, you're just annoying.
You're like a little, you're probably sick or something like that.
You definitely want to stick to friends.
I don't care for him, he's banned on the show.
You're about to know.
You don't tell me what I'm allowed and not allowed to.
You're not my mama, okay?
But she's the one that can tell me shit, maybe my sister too, but anybody else, I don't
listen to.
and I do have to defer to powerful women.
So how are we doing guys though?
Oh my gosh, it's fluctuating a little bit.
I mean, I'll address any questions.
Yeah, but I will, I'll keep using it a little bit.
How do I look actually, by the way?
Am I looking like too much like Jeffrey Dahmer?
And I noticed like they were playing like the video fast.
Like it's okay, you don't have to play my videos fast,
Sam, unless you're like trying to save time.
I'm not gonna ever strike anybody for playing my video.
I'm not gonna ever strike anybody.
I don't.
I believe in striking people. I believe in freedom of speech and stuff.
Even if I hate the person, I'm not going to fuck with their lifestyle or whatever.
I'm just going to let them do what they want to do. Just be them.
I don't like to interfere with people.
Constantly, I'm being interfered with, but I'm still here, so I can't complain.
So, why don't we do some astrology?
I can actually impress somebody.
I'll do a magic trick.
Sun sign your moon sign, and if you want to your ascendant sign, I might leave for like a minute
Come on a song or something. I'll be back a few minutes
Get the custom song for you about your you and your sun sign and ascendant and it's like I mean
I'm able to do it best
But it will be a meeting and then this I will do free for the first person to ask for
Just to give me those three signs though. Yeah, you do all three that might be different for each side and then I'm gonna
Yeah, you'll you'll do like it. I'm gonna impress everybody with my talent
But I really do believe in like creating this music to have a better
Basically the music right now today in the world is programming brainwashing social engineering
There's like a purpose behind it and nobody really just like listens to the meaning
But it's like subconsciously we're picking up the meaning of this music, right?
And so it's programming us very it's like very effectively
And so how about like, you know, write your own music or songs or have the songs be relevant to you and something about you?
It's more positive, especially when it's music. Music is so powerful. It's definitely like a form of magic.
It's like speech, but like, you know, a beautified type of speech. It's like exercising the voice.
Hey guys, how we can have the Chris gay music and sound or be what it how are you doing erby?
Are you up? Y'all cool?
Um, I'll remod you if you want. I don't know if you want to be a little more people just
It doesn't really matter. I prefer not that people are mods because then if they do lose it eventually
They don't be mad, but I think it's like better. Okay. Sorry. I wouldn't McDonald's
Biting in the chat. Is any problematic lava here lava is here for the cats and the
They get to be a a mod. Okay. How are we doing in a chat today? Okay. Who's a little bit warm?
Okay, if hopefully no one's timed out, like, um, Rose doesn't, um, hi people. Where's that funny part though?
There's a funny part. Oh, did I, I'm already closed. I'm already closed, I guess. Okay.
We all happy? Okay. What else we got? Let me see. Ooh, it's warm.
i shouldn't have thought our reign was fried
said i could win but the chat just sighed won't you banish me
they said i wasn't reasonable nothing was debatable
we didn't see is that i am still me the rose red roses and roses are red roses
roses are d roses are red rose are red rose are red i'm not sure how you how i
Don't feel good in your in your kitty nose. You mean your cat, right? Sometimes people use a euphemism
Okay, what else do we have? Let's see. We have been a nice day everybody
Okay, this is how that and I think our G loved the song
You said it sounded like Bobby Brown
If you want to back I'll give it back, you know, I'll just respect everyone's wishes. I'm gonna push you into
I'm fire everybody gotta take names in the air like a trial. I didn't make banning out pick a side prove
You're one of us funny how fast that support turns to pressure and disgust. I said, I don't know the story
I'm a sign enough on claims you want instant verdicts. I don't play those games
No pay for then I'm asking for more that defense does me check in the floor
Supposed to be you were back in me like in the show till I didn't follow where you wanted me to go
This is my, not your, immunity.
Turns to a pile on,
In voices yelling different names on the stage.
Everyone knows, yeah, everyone says.
Nobody stops to question the threads.
Poof in the DMs, I didn't review.
Poof, you decided it was already true.
You want me to crowd-made case, then punish me.
When I don't ban a few people now,
I'm with the games you play.
You push, I call, then call it.
I can the show, till I didn't follow
where you wanted me to go.
i trace it cause no one's trying to speak over me but this is my you made you judge now executioner
live in my chat just to keep you standing where i choose to be you're kissing me you're kissing me
are you kissing you give me kisses okay i'll give you a few minutes if anyone wants to come up
oh when you can nap you when you can nap you would you i love you too
This isn't my, I guess it was called my,
our FaZe, my Rumorodio.
Here, this one's good.
Oh, I know, you want country music?
You want country music?
Oh, you want country music?
Okay, what did I just do?
All right, babe.
Okay, you're kissing?
Okay.
With a story in your tongue,
I was even good.
Got smoke, but no flame.
Just a trail of me.
Take a head, it's so cause the sun comes up.
BG and the MK Ultra Mind Control Sex Kitty Monarch Butterfly Program.
I'm not going to say that again because I might mess it up.
Before I start this video, I want to thank everybody that like, comment, share and subscribe.
I see it.
God see it.
Blessings to you and your situations.
Just in case you don't make it to the end of the video, I wanted to thank you now.
Thank you.
And I mean that.
So I'm watching Nino Brown.
I'm pretty sure everybody is familiar with who Nino Brown is.
The guy that you see right now on the screen with the crown on.
I'm subscribed.
I've been subscribed to Nino Brown for years.
He make me laugh and he's conscious.
He give praises to the most high.
And I just like the guy, he make me feel like a vibe high.
So I'm listening to Nino Brown and he has a question.
I'm gonna answer the question that Nino Brown have
in this video.
Listen to the question.
Bitch, if you could have any woman in the world,
would you want some fire shit that nobody had before
or would you want a bra that everybody in the industry
I'm trying to figure out why these rappers and these ballplayers and these actors all
recycle the same fire whip.
This shit don't make no sense.
Can somebody help me make it make sense?
I'ma make it make sense.
He just got out of prison, and you would think he'll be looking for a girl that nobody's been with.
Instead, he ain't caught in BDM, trying to pull a ditty on Stefan Diz, B.M.
For some apparent reason, Poushastik went off set left overs.
All that goddamn money Poushastik said he got, and you want what another man had.
Ruby Rose. She's at the top of the food chain. She done been with rockers, ballplayers, and comedians.
She was with Druskin just last year. Cam Newton, DDG, Lil Yachty,
Playboy Cardi, Travis Scott. She done been with everybody. But if you go ask somebody on the internet who they want.
Who be wronged?
They chose who be wronged after everybody.
If I get school in with the high school,
we won't let nobody else in the high school won't.
I don't know what we need.
You see what Nino Brown is seeing is a program.
Nino Brown, brother Nino Brown, you are seeing a program.
There's a lot of people right now.
They don't see this program.
But Nino Brown, he see the program.
I hope you see the program.
You gotta get rich, all they want is the same shit that they see somebody else done been with.
Selena Powell, she a well known 304 that everybody know, but yet there's a line of rich rockers
and ball player waiting to be with her next.
These men are massively goddamn rich and could be with any woman in the world.
They could even go get the goddamn virgin married that nobody been with.
But yet they won't, what they play a partner just had.
The Kardashians.
They got a history of destroying men,
and you would have thought that that would have made
some of the most successful men in the world.
They don't know where to keep.
They got them distanced from me, got them fetches.
But no.
I always ask that question.
You see, I've seen beautiful nurses.
I've seen beautiful women that was professionals, that was smart.
I'm talking about bodies out of this world.
They will intimidate the average guy.
And you mean to tell me these rappers, these athletes and entertainers
are recycling the same women?
This has to be a program, man.
I'm going to break it down. It's a program.
They attracted moe robbers, moe ball players, moe actors, and turning their heads in the
crack adders and got them alcoholists, and they all going broke and losing their mind.
Kanye, Lamar, hold on, she didn't like that girl just now you're Michelle, she would
just carry a WNBA young one paper.
Why the hell did John T. Murray gonna put a goddamn baby in her?
They want what the other rapper did, hey, and she try-
Why would Kanye West? Kanye West is very intelligent.
Kanye West is a musical genius. Why would he marry a woman?
made a sex tape with Ray J. Not only did she make a sex tape, she made a sex tape
with a guy that isn't even on day level. Why? I'm gonna tell you why. I'm gonna tell
you why.
I'm gonna get rid of God damn the ball player cause he done heard it got their leg and go
Ari Thomas the train factor. She was just with that thing, G Herbo. And here come money bag coming
from your head and won't sell what G Herbo got. And listen, the majority of these sex kittens,
because that's who these women are. Sex kittens. The majority of these sex kittens don't even look good.
Like I said, I've seen regular women, regular women with money, regular women that can think
for themselves, regular women.
That was beautiful, man.
And none of these rappers, entertainers, they're not checking for them.
They're checking for these MK Ultra, Mind Control, Monarch Butterfly, Sex Kittens.
Because Nino Brown, he want to know why.
He want to know why when the person get rich,
when they get successful, they run to these women.
This is crazy, man, or it's a program.
Listen to Cat Williams a couple of months ago.
Cat Williams, he talked about this a little bit.
Let's go back to Cat Williams.
each thing I'm saying.
I don't have harbor any resentment
to any of these entities because I can't be jealous.
I've never seen them have anything that I ever wanted.
If you sign up for their program, you get a light skin.
weird-faced wife that never do an interview.
Oh, her true.
Listen, in 20 years, won't do an interview.
Nobody's ever talked to her.
And she's never been interviewed anywhere.
And now, understand, I'm not talking about one person.
What I just told you applies to seven people.
How they all be resentment to any of these entities
because I can't be jealous.
I've never seen them have anything that I ever wanted.
If you sign up for their program you get a light skin
Weird-faced wife that never do an interview
Listen if you sign up for their program
You get a amber rose
If you sign up for their program you get a sex
kidding
MK ultra mind control monarch butterfly
Sex kiddin. Yes, these women are owned
There's people that own people
Yes, and when you sign up for their program
You get one of them. You know who they are
because
When you see them in the photos
You always see them in leopard print
Look at the video
Everybody that you see in leopard print in more
Look, I could pull up so many videos of Little Nas X.
I could pull up videos of Michael B. Jarton and Tom Cruise.
You know how people have the pictures of them
throwing up the 666, the blood sign,
and putting it over their eye?
And people say that this is one of their symbols.
Well, the leper print is also
It's because of there's people. He's not an animal or own people
If you go out there right now and get a record deal
Inside of that contract for a lot of people
It comes with a sex kitten one of these females a
Lot of times the sex kitten is the handler of the entertainer or the athlete
Nino Brown what you are looking at is the sex kid in program
This is why they recycled the same women because these women in their contract
And when they tell these women a bark they bark and when they tell these women to crawl
They crawl they also feed off of the feminine energy of the woman that they went the sex kid in
There's also men that sex kitten and if you ever see one of these
Entertainers these these actors or athletes if you ever see them in this leopard print and in there and they're in the photos
Then you best believe that there's sex kittens and at any time
They can get a phone call and that phone call tells them to go to Dubai
And they go to Dubai
They sleep with old men, old women, people, people that's not even in this dimension.
Jimi Hendrix, Jimi Hendrix, you mean to tell me Jimi Hendrix?
You mean to tell me Whitney Houston, yes, I know Whitney Houston was a sex kitten.
You see, when these sex kittens get married, this is what drives their partner crazy, because
at any time these sex kittens, they can get a phone call.
And all of a sudden, they're surrounded by 15 72 year old guys, 65 year old guys with
shriveled penises that want to get their ass ate.
It's beautiful sex kittens out there.
Some of the women that we worship, that we look at, Cardi B, I'm talking about Nicki
Minaj, I'm talking about all of them.
Go look at the pictures.
Type up.
Okay.
Type up Nicki Minaj Leopard print type up little Nas X Leopard print and watch how many
Photos come up with them with Leopard print and then type up
Ice Cube Leopard Print. Type up LLQJ Leopard Print and see how you don't see no damn Leopard Print
with them guys. There are some people that you're going to see with the Leopard Print on
and trust me these people are owned. So let's go back to what Nino Brown is talking about.
You know Brown want to know why do all of these rappers
Recycled the same women now. There's people out there that would say
It's because they're in the same circle
But I'm here to say that these women are sex kittens like doja cat
These women's are sex kittens and when you sign the contract you get a sex kitten
You get the rub on them and kiss on them and take pictures and as soon as the contract is over
They go to the next person
It's like when you sell your soul to Satan
You you get a lot of gifts a lot of perks
And you say, yeah, I want the steak and the lobster.
I want this car.
I want this type of house, this type of chain.
And this type of woman.
They say, OK, what type of woman do you want?
This is the list of women that you can get.
Do you want Doja Cat?
We got Doja Cat.
We can give you Doja Cat because Doja Cat is a sex kitten.
Do you like boys?
We can give you Lil Nas X if you won't.
And there's a list of other people that we can give you.
I'm really picturing these people sitting up
in front of a CEO, a high-powered person.
And this person convincing them to sell
all of their manifestation gifts,
all of their sacred knowledge and their energy,
their connection with the most time to sell it.
And they say, look, you can eat all of this,
you can smoke all of this, you could do all of this,
you can go to all of these places in the world,
and you can have all of these women on the list.
And this person, look, up and down the list,
and they see all types of names they wouldn't even believe.
They say, you mean to tell me.
Then I can get into a relationship with Cardi B and they say yeah, we'll make it happen
then all of a sudden this person come out with a with an album they have a
Hit record it goes platinum and in the next six months you see them engaged to Cardi B
All of this shit is fake man, and I know you know
What I'm talking about all praises to the most high. Thank you to everybody that like comment share and subscribe
I see it. God see it. Blessings to you in your situations